Wh... You're
suggesting
(Sheldon:)that I have emotional issues
below my consciousness
which drive my behavior,
(Sheldon:)thus causing me to lash out
at anything or anyone
(Sheldon:)that threatens
my intellectual superiority.
(Leonard:)Might be something
to think about.
(Sheldon:)Leonard?
(Sheldon:)Yeah.
(Sheldon:)Howard's allergic to peanuts.
(Sheldon:)How can I use that against him?
(Raj:)Hey.
(Sheldon:)Okay, now that everyone's here,
we can begin.
(Howard:)Before we do,
I just talked to Leonard.
(Howard:)And if you're gonna
(Howard:)spend all your time
trying to belittle me
(Howard:)by making this class
unnecessarily hard,
(Howard:)then I'm out.
(Howard:)But if you're interested
in making
(Howard:)a sincere effort
to be a good teacher,
(Howard:)then I'm willing
to give this a shot.
(Sheldon:)I suppose that's a fair request.
(Sheldon:)There's no reason we both can't
benefit from this experience.